import 'package:english_test/models/entities/answer_question_entity.dart';

List<AnswerQuestionEntity> listAnswerReading1 = [
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R11",
    answer: "Raising a family of great horned owls",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R12",
    answer: "a sound",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R13",
    answer: "is an active process",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R14",
    answer: "may inhabit a previously used nest",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R15",
    answer: "to sit on the nest",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R16",
    answer: "the eggs",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R17",
    answer: "nuts and seeds",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R18",
    answer: "the young birds",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R19",
    answer: "They probably don't see their young after November.",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R110",
    answer: "tired of",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R111",
    answer: "Getting started on the trip west",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R112",
    answer: "was usually by steamboat",
  ),
  AnswerQuestionEntity(
    idAnswerQuestion: "R113",
    answer: "a point of departure",
  ),
];
